It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
How have you been?
元気してた?
Well, well, I'm fine.
まあ、 まあ、元気です
fine?
元気?
It's kind of cute again.
またなんか可愛くなったね
Well, that's not true.
えー、そんなことないですよ
lie?
嘘?
TRUE?
本当?
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですよ
That's it now.
今あれだもんね
Well, originally, I was an idol.
あれっていうか、もともと、 アイドルやってたことね
yes.
はい
More like an idol or a research student.
アイドルっていうか、 研究生みたいな
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
What group were you in?
どこのグループでしたっけ?
Just don't say that.
それをちょっと言わないって
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうだね
Stop that, what are you doing now?
それやめて、今は何してるの?
At the company we met, I was aiming to become an actress.
会う会社で、 会社っていうか女優を 目指してて、
So, I'm doing a lot of things right now.
それで、今いろいろ やってるっていうか、
I feel like I'm doing my best.
頑張ってる感じでやってます
I agree.
そうだね
I'm currently trying to become an actress.
今女優目指して やってるんだね
What do you think?
どうですか?
What about work?
仕事の方は?
From that.
あれ から
Ah, something lately.
あー、なんか、 最近、
When I was cast in a drama, even though it was called a drama,
ド ラマの 出演が決まって、 ドラマって言っても、
It's like that little local thing at a late-night party.
深夜会の あの、地方の ちっちゃいような
Seriously?
マジで?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Local?
地方の?
But it's a drama, right?
でも、ちゃんとドラマ でしょ?
Well, drama.
まあ、ドラマ
That's amazing!
すごいじゃん!
I did my best.
頑張りました
Congratulations!
おめでとう!
There are lines and things like that.
セリフとかあるんだ
yes.
はい
It's like practicing, practicing, practicing.
練習して、 練 習して、稽古みたいな
Then, steadily step up your work.
じゃあ、着実に あれだね、仕事を ステップアップしていって
That's right.
んだ ね
Since then, it has become an edge, and if you make one camera, you have an edge.
あれからエッジ、 カメラ1回作ればエッジしたわけじゃん
Have you gotten any kind of edge since then?
あれから、なんか エッジした?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Well, I guess I haven't.
なんていうか、してないかな
I haven't.
してないです
All of a sudden, even the bottom becomes a joke.
急にね、下もネタになっちゃうんですけど
Haven't you?
してないの?
I haven't.
してないです
But yeah, it's like that, when a drama appears, etc.
でもさ、なんかそういうさ、 ドラマ出るとかさ、
I guess you could say that there are quite a lot of good-looking guys in there.
結構イケメン入り とか言うわけでしょ
So, is there anything you can do with someone like that?
で、 そういう人とさ、なんか ないの?
No, not at all.
いや、全然ないです
lie?
嘘?
Great, for the producers etc. Ah,
えらい、プロデューサーさんとかに あー、
it is...
それは...
Does that exist?
それはあるの?
No, now.
いや、 今、
A long time ago?
なんか 昔?
It's the idol era, right?
アイドル時代でしょ?
I don't think you feel that way every time.
お前も、毎回そういう感じじゃない気がするよ
When I was an idol, with the producer,
アイドルやってる時に プロデューサーさんと、
Like.
みたいな
Did you do it?
しましたっけ?
Did you do that?
したっけ?
I see.
そっか
I'll give you a little support.
ちょっと応援します、僕は
It's been a while.
久 しぶりってことで
So, let's have fun.
だから ね、 楽しみましょう
It's cute, after all.
かわいいな、やっぱり
Are you touching me like this?
こんな感じで触ってくるの?
What an amazing person.
なんか、えらい人って
Don't touch me.
触ってくるんじゃなくて
But I still can't refuse.
でも、やっぱり、 断れない
Like.
みたい な
You're so thin, really.
ほっそいね、ほんとに
This makes me want to touch it.
触りたくなっちゃうね、これね
Eh, so thin.
え、ほっそい
There.
そ こ
I saw the pants.
パンツ見ちゃいました
I'm starting to like it.
気に入ってくる
No, it's been a while.
いや、久しぶりなんだから
Hey, I was just standing there.
ちょっとさ、立ってたから
You’ve always wanted to hedge, haven’t you?
ずっとヘッジしたかったでしょ?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Good job, right?
良ししたよね
It's cute, it's underneath.
かわいいね、下に入ってて
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It's me.
自分です
Open it.
開いてごらん
Please open it.
開 いてごらん
I'm twitching.
ひくひくしてる
Are you moving it?
動かしてる?
It's moving.
動いてるよ
Try moving it.
動かしてみて
It's moving.
動いてる
動
Try it.
か してみて
Would you like to open a mangoki?
マンゴキ開いてごらん?
Have you ever used this?
これ使ったことある?
Can I have you push me out?
押し付け出してもらっていい?